{
  "id": "famous-bands-recall",
  "title": "Famous Bands Recall",
  "description": "How well do you remember the greatest bands in music history?",
  "gameCategory": "memory-games",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-1",
      "question": "Which band was originally known as 'The Quarrymen'?",
      "options": [
        "The Kinks",
        "The Rolling Stones",
        "The Who",
        "The Beatles"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-2",
      "question": "Who was the lead guitarist of Led Zeppelin?",
      "options": [
        "Jeff Beck",
        "Jimmy Page",
        "Eric Clapton",
        "Jimi Hendrix"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-3",
      "question": "Which band released the hit song 'Bohemian Rhapsody'?",
      "options": [
        "Genesis",
        "Pink Floyd",
        "Yes",
        "Queen"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-4",
      "question": "How many original members were in The Beach Boys?",
      "options": [
        "3",
        "4",
        "6",
        "5"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-5",
      "question": "Which band's drummer was Keith Moon?",
      "options": [
        "Led Zeppelin",
        "The Rolling Stones",
        "Cream",
        "The Who"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-6",
      "question": "Mick Jagger is the frontman of which legendary band?",
      "options": [
        "The Yardbirds",
        "The Rolling Stones",
        "The Kinks",
        "The Animals"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-7",
      "question": "Which band released the album 'The Joshua Tree'?",
      "options": [
        "Radiohead",
        "U2",
        "R.E.M.",
        "Coldplay"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-8",
      "question": "The Bee Gees were originally from which country?",
      "options": [
        "Australia",
        "United States",
        "England",
        "Ireland"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-9",
      "question": "Which band featured the songwriting duo of Lennon and McCartney?",
      "options": [
        "The Beatles",
        "The Everly Brothers",
        "The Righteous Brothers",
        "Simon & Garfunkel"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-10",
      "question": "Which country did ABBA originate from?",
      "options": [
        "Finland",
        "Denmark",
        "Norway",
        "Sweden"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-11",
      "question": "Who was the lead singer of The Doors?",
      "options": [
        "Janis Joplin",
        "Robert Plant",
        "Roger Daltrey",
        "Jim Morrison"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-12",
      "question": "Which band is known for the songs 'Comfortably Numb' and 'Wish You Were Here'?",
      "options": [
        "Pink Floyd",
        "King Crimson",
        "Genesis",
        "Jethro Tull"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-13",
      "question": "Freddie Mercury was born in which country?",
      "options": [
        "India",
        "Zanzibar (Tanzania)",
        "England",
        "Iran"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-14",
      "question": "Which band recorded the song 'Don't Stop Believin''?",
      "options": [
        "Styx",
        "Foreigner",
        "REO Speedwagon",
        "Journey"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": "famous-bands-recall-15",
      "question": "Which band was inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame in 1995 on their first year of eligibility?",
      "options": [
        "Led Zeppelin",
        "The Allman Brothers Band",
        "The Grateful Dead",
        "Pink Floyd"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ]
}
